{
    "id": "9764ce0d9c6d4b8d8da2ae8966c7b5f5",
    "title": "Continuous Or Simple Tense",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "905336b30d454e63aee57e2e61dfb8b4",
            "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………….. the manager in the afternoon.",
                    "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about a future event that is already planned.",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… his voice.",
                    "description": "The verb like is hardly ever used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "a liking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I called him because I …………………………. to talk.",
                    "description": "Want is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "wanted",
                        "was wanting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ……………………………. hard.",
                    "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about actions or situations that are going on at the moment of speaking. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "rains",
                        "is raining"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………….. that education should be free for all.",
                    "description": "Believe is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "believe",
                        "am believing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………….. that we are committing a mistake.",
                    "description": "When feel means have an opinion, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "feel",
                        "am feeling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………….. how to ride a bicycle.",
                    "description": "Know is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "am knowing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… my holidays right now.",
                    "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about ongoing situations.",
                    "answers": [
                        "enjoy",
                        "am enjoying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………………… when they arrived.",
                    "description": "The past continuous is used to talk about the longer background action that was in progress when another action occurred.",
                    "answers": [
                        "slept",
                        "is sleeping",
                        "was sleeping"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ………………………… difficult now.",
                    "description": "Look is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "looks",
                        "is looking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………………… to a hill tribe.",
                    "description": "Belong is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "belongs",
                        "is belonging"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………. 50 kg last month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was weighing",
                        "weighed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}